易考范文二十三
As is depicted in the above drawing, a waiter,
using “payment in advance” as a preferential measure,
sets a trap for the customer in reality.
What is revealed in the drawing is a social phenomenon that
has aroused nationwide concerns.
Nowadays, in order to attract more customers,
a great number of businessmen adopt the favorable strategy of advance payment,
promising that consumers are entitled to discounts
as long as they pay for the service beforehand.
As can be expected, many a consumer can hardly resist those tempting discounts
and pays a large sum of money in advance.
However, instead of keeping their word to offer service,
some businessmen flee with the money they swindle out of the customers,
while the latter have to accept bad luck.
I assume this hard nut can be cracked in light of the following aspects.
First of all, consumers should be more cautious
and pay more attention to the credit of the shop.
Secondly, the Consumer's Association is supposed to take effective measures
to protect the consumers' rights.
What's more, it is vital for the businessmen to realize that
conning consumers can do most harm to nobody but themselves in the end
and that they'd better win a good credit for the sake of long-run profit.